<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>IceCereal</title>
    <link>http://icecereal.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on IceCereal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 01:12:13 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://icecereal.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>I Set Up a PiHole</title>
      <link>http://icecereal.github.io/blog/i-set-up-a-pihole/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 01:12:13 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://icecereal.github.io/blog/i-set-up-a-pihole/</guid>
      <description>Okay, so this wasn&amp;rsquo;t on my To-Do List but I really wanted to do this for a looong time&amp;hellip; so I did it 5 minutes ago. A couple of days ago, I bought a Raspberry Pi 4 (1Gb RAM) and decided to set up a PiHole. Pi-hole is a Linux network-level advertisement and Internet tracker blocking application which acts as a DNS sinkhole, intended for use on a private network. is what Wikipedia says and that&amp;rsquo;s better than whatever I could have said.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Way Too Soon for a Next Post</title>
      <link>http://icecereal.github.io/blog/way-too-soon-for-a-next-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 18:17:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://icecereal.github.io/blog/way-too-soon-for-a-next-post/</guid>
      <description>&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Sigh, yes. I know. This is probably way too soon for a next post on my blog, but hey, I&amp;rsquo;m happy that I&amp;rsquo;m keeping up with Point # 1 of my To-Do list for this winter.
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Anyway, the reason for this post is that I&amp;rsquo;m quite excited about To-Do list Point # 2. I&amp;rsquo;ve just spoken to the Professor about the project we&amp;rsquo;re going to be working on. We have a clear direction of what needs to be done this winter and most of next semester.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Init D</title>
      <link>http://icecereal.github.io/blog/init-d/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 15:29:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://icecereal.github.io/blog/init-d/</guid>
      <description>&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Okay, so I&amp;rsquo;ve been putting this off for a very long time, but it&amp;rsquo;s time I do it. I have the time, I&amp;rsquo;m bored, I&amp;rsquo;m alone in the library with no one to distract me, I have a hot cup of coffee, and I have good music playing on my headphones. I want this blog to be a place where I can jot down my ideas, make a To-Do list, and track my progress in discrete intervals of time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>http://icecereal.github.io/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 17:12:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://icecereal.github.io/projects/</guid>
      <description>These are the projects I have worked on / I am working on. These are displayed in random order.
MemeTaker_Bot  One of the first bots I developed. This bot was developed to fetch a meme from 4 defined subreddits and download the meme using wget. This program was called by my more, ambitious SuperUserBot_V2. It also makes sure that the meme has not been downloaded before.
SuperUserBot_V2  This is the second version of my first Discord Bot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About_Me</title>
      <link>http://icecereal.github.io/about_me/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 1970 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://icecereal.github.io/about_me/</guid>
      <description>Name: Raghav NS
Date Of Birth: 1999-Oct-30
Email: raghav170555@mechyd.ac.in
Intro: I like to program. I started to code in 7th grade when I learnt BASIC after which I learnt C in 8th grade. 2 years later, I started learning C++ in 11th and 12th grade. I like anime, playing instruments, tinkering with electronics, listening to Lo-Fi and drinking juice. I want to set up a company and be an entreprenur&amp;hellip; or do a PhD in Computer Science&amp;hellip; or both.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>