<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on IceCereal</title>
    <link>http://icecereal.github.io/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on IceCereal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2020 21:09:47 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://icecereal.github.io/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Shutting Down of Covindia</title>
      <link>http://icecereal.github.io/blog/the-shutting-down-of-covindia/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2020 21:09:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://icecereal.github.io/blog/the-shutting-down-of-covindia/</guid>
      <description>On 2020-May-31 16:00:00, covindia.com shut down after nearly 2.5 months of running. This is the email that I sent out to the team and the university management:
 Greetings Everyone,
What started out as an idea in a meeting room in the Faculty Office on the first floor on 12th March, 2020 turned into something colossal over the past two months. 11-ish weeks of working relentlessly, persistently and non-stop have culminated into what has been the biggest and most socially impacting project that I have ever been a part of, Covindia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Made a Website That Hit a Million Views in 2 Weeks</title>
      <link>http://icecereal.github.io/blog/i-made-a-website-that-hit-a-million-views-in-2-weeks/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 00:14:20 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://icecereal.github.io/blog/i-made-a-website-that-hit-a-million-views-in-2-weeks/</guid>
      <description>Oh boy, this is a big one. A realllllly big one. So big, in fact, it may be the coolest blog post I&amp;rsquo;ve ever written. Ever.
TL;DR at the bottom
Note: This website looks nice on laptops. The images zoom in when you hover over them. That don&amp;rsquo;t happen on da phone, yo 🤘. Also this title is slightly click-baity. I did set up the website that touched a million views in 2 weeks, but there was a team of like 7-8 people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How I Hacked My Uni&#39;s Internship Portal</title>
      <link>http://icecereal.github.io/blog/how-i-hacked-my-unis-internship-portal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 10:15:55 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://icecereal.github.io/blog/how-i-hacked-my-unis-internship-portal/</guid>
      <description>Warning: This is low-key illegal. I&amp;rsquo;m very fortunate that the parties involved took it in a good manner and didn&amp;rsquo;t suspend me. Note to future self: Don&amp;rsquo;t do stupid shit.
Note to the reader: I use College and University interchangably because my College is almost about to be a Uni soon, so yeah.
TL;DR at the bottom
Well, this is going to be a looong and glorious post. This is the story of how a young man became the most powerful person on his campus for around 8 hours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Second Place in a Hackathon</title>
      <link>http://icecereal.github.io/blog/second-place-in-a-hackathon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 15:11:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://icecereal.github.io/blog/second-place-in-a-hackathon/</guid>
      <description>TL;DR at the bottom
On 23rd January, The Entrepreneurship &amp;amp; Innovation Cell (EIC) of our college conducted their annual ESummit. They had a few events out of which one was The Startup Sprint: a 30 hour long hackathon meant for students who wanted to start a company. It focused ~60% on the Business Part and ~40% on the Technology Part. The hackathon began on Thursday afternoon at 2pm and was to end on Friday evening at 8pm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two Weeks in the New Sem</title>
      <link>http://icecereal.github.io/blog/two-weeks-in-the-new-sem/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 14:22:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://icecereal.github.io/blog/two-weeks-in-the-new-sem/</guid>
      <description>Previously, on the blog: Winter Vacation is Done
Am I looking forward to next semester? I&#39;m not sure. These are the courses I have: - Computer Networks (9 / 10 excited 🎉🎉) - Web Programming (7 / 10 excited) - Software Engineering (6 / 10 excited) - Machine Learning (6 / 10 excited) - High Performance Computing (10 / 10 excited 🎉🎉🎉) - Third Year Team Project - This is variable - Elective-1 - I still have to choose this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working With Android Studio</title>
      <link>http://icecereal.github.io/blog/working-with-android-studio/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 00:30:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://icecereal.github.io/blog/working-with-android-studio/</guid>
      <description>5 of my friends and I have a pretty cool idea for an app. We&amp;rsquo;ve been discussing it non-stop for the past 4-5 days and trying to decide what our app should be. It all started from a simple and primitive idea and it evolved to a pretty decent stage now. I&amp;rsquo;m not going to discuss the app idea here because it&amp;rsquo;s in its primitive stage (and what if my 1 reader (including me) steals the idea?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Favorite Indie Band Uploaded A Story About Me</title>
      <link>http://icecereal.github.io/blog/my-favorite-indie-band-uploaded-a-story-about-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 22:28:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://icecereal.github.io/blog/my-favorite-indie-band-uploaded-a-story-about-me/</guid>
      <description>TL;DR at the bottom
I&amp;rsquo;m ecstatic. I love a band called Peach Pit and have been obsessed with them for around a year now. Their album Being So Normal has to be my most listened to album of all time. Every song in the album is incredible. The dreamy guitar solos by Chris, Neil&amp;rsquo;s hypnotic singing, Peter&amp;rsquo;s very subtle yet very prominent bass, and Mikey&amp;rsquo;s perfect drums working in such amazing sync is what makes each song brilliant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Winter Vacation Is Done</title>
      <link>http://icecereal.github.io/blog/winter-vacation-is-done/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 21:44:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://icecereal.github.io/blog/winter-vacation-is-done/</guid>
      <description>Well, my winter vacation has come to an end. I can&amp;rsquo;t believe time flew this fast. I&amp;rsquo;m usually excited to go back to college, but this is the first time in 2 1/2 years that I&amp;rsquo;m not too excited to go back to college. It&amp;rsquo;s not because next semester is dreadful (it isn&amp;rsquo;t, we have HPC!!!), it&amp;rsquo;s because I&amp;rsquo;m going to miss my home. This past month was relaxing, productive and mainly a big breather for me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Last Post of the Decade</title>
      <link>http://icecereal.github.io/blog/last-post-of-the-decade/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 22:40:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://icecereal.github.io/blog/last-post-of-the-decade/</guid>
      <description>Well, I guess this is the last post of the decade. I&amp;rsquo;m listening to Lo-Fi and working on TEDx&amp;rsquo;s website right now. A fitting way to end the decade. Lo-Fi.
I went to a market meant for electronics yesterday to buy some electronic components for the Music Reactive Desk Lamp I wanted to work on. I did buy some earlier, but for some reason, the LED Light Strip that I bought wasn&amp;rsquo;t working (it was showing random colors).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tips Fedora 31</title>
      <link>http://icecereal.github.io/blog/tips-fedora-31/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2019 12:48:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://icecereal.github.io/blog/tips-fedora-31/</guid>
      <description>Okay, I got bored. Really bored. So what do all cool kids do when they&amp;rsquo;re bored? Change their OS, obviously 🙄. Yes, I changed my OS. Again. Which makes it the 4th time I&amp;rsquo;ve formatted my computer this year (excluding my Desktop format). I was running Ubuntu 19.10 (Eoan Ermine) for around 2 months when I felt it to be a bit heavy and a bit buggy. I also had only one partition of 2Tb size which I couldn&amp;rsquo;t really shrink into multiple partitions becuase I encrypted it with LUKS2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pass, My New Password Manager</title>
      <link>http://icecereal.github.io/blog/pass-my-new-password-manager/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2019 12:11:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://icecereal.github.io/blog/pass-my-new-password-manager/</guid>
      <description>It seems as if I do everything but the tasks on my To-Do list. I&amp;rsquo;ve been using Firefox&amp;rsquo;s Lockwise (In-Built Password Manager) for a decent amount of time now and I decided that it was finally time to move on from an external password manager to my own password managing system. I started looking for Unix Password Managers and there were a few. After some consideration, I settled for Pass, a beautiful password manager that works on GPG and simplicity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Set Up a PiHole</title>
      <link>http://icecereal.github.io/blog/i-set-up-a-pihole/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 01:12:13 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://icecereal.github.io/blog/i-set-up-a-pihole/</guid>
      <description>Okay, so this wasn&amp;rsquo;t on my To-Do List but I really wanted to do this for a looong time&amp;hellip; so I did it 5 minutes ago. A couple of days ago, I bought a Raspberry Pi 4 (1Gb RAM) and decided to set up a PiHole. Pi-hole is a Linux network-level advertisement and Internet tracker blocking application which acts as a DNS sinkhole, intended for use on a private network. is what Wikipedia says and that&amp;rsquo;s better than whatever I could have said.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Way Too Soon for a Next Post</title>
      <link>http://icecereal.github.io/blog/way-too-soon-for-a-next-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 18:17:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://icecereal.github.io/blog/way-too-soon-for-a-next-post/</guid>
      <description>Sigh, yes. I know. This is probably way too soon for a next post on my blog, but hey, I&amp;rsquo;m happy that I&amp;rsquo;m keeping up with Point # 1 of my To-Do list for this winter.
 Anyway, the reason for this post is that I&amp;rsquo;m quite excited about To-Do list Point # 2. I&amp;rsquo;ve just spoken to the Professor about the project we&amp;rsquo;re going to be working on. We have a clear direction of what needs to be done this winter and most of next semester.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Init D</title>
      <link>http://icecereal.github.io/blog/init-d/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 15:29:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://icecereal.github.io/blog/init-d/</guid>
      <description>Okay, so I&amp;rsquo;ve been putting this off for a very long time, but it&amp;rsquo;s time I do it. I have the time, I&amp;rsquo;m bored, I&amp;rsquo;m alone in the library with no one to distract me, I have a hot cup of coffee, and I have good music playing on my headphones. I want this blog to be a place where I can jot down my ideas, make a To-Do list, and track my progress in discrete intervals of time.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>